--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
w
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
ww
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.H
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HD
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDc
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcm
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmc
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmct
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmct.
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmct.c
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmct.co
招募Q號:76846146
--==CMCT團隊 榮譽出品==--
影片壓制: 九洲客  字幕調校: 子賀居士
www.HDcmct.com
招募Q號:76846146
片名: 全金屬外殼
America has heard the bugle call
美國聽到號角聲
And you know it involves us one and all
你知它和我們整體有關
"I don't suppose that war will ever end
我不認為戰爭會結束
There's fighting that will break us up again
這場戰爭使我們分離
Good-bye, my darling
再會 親愛的
Hello, Vietnam
喂! 越南
I'm here to take a battle to be won
我來這裏贏取勝利
Kiss me good-bye
和我吻別
And write me while I'm gone
我出外作戰你須與我通信
"Good-bye, my sweetheart "
再見 甜心
Hello, Vietnam
喂! 越南
I am Gunnery Sergeant Hartman,
我是海軍陸戰隊中士哈特曼
your senior drill instructor.
是你們的高級訓練教官
You will speak
除非我先說話...
only when spoken to
你們不得擅自開口
The first and last words out of your sewers will be "Sir! "
你們跟我說話首尾都要冠以"長官"一詞
Do you maggots understand?
你們這些蛆蟲明白嗎?
Sir, yes, sir!
長官 是 長官
I can't hear you.Sound off like you got a pair.
我聽不到 該用男子漢般的氣概回答
If you ladies leave my island,
你們這些"女士"受新兵訓練後
if you survive recruit training...
"倖存"者才可以離開我的島
...you will be a weapon,
你們將是件武器
a minister of death, praying for war.
死亡執行者 戰爭祈求者
But until that day, you are pukes!
在上前線前 你們全是嘔吐物
The lowest form of life on Earth.
地球最低等的生物
You are not even human fucking beings!
你們不是他媽的人類
You are only unorganized,grab-asstic pieces of amphibian shit!
你們只是一群烏合之眾的廢物
Because I am hard,
我苛刻嚴厲
you won't like me.
你們不會喜歡我
The more you hate me,the more you'll learn.
但你們越恨我便學得越多
I am hard, but I am fair!
我雖嚴格但公正
There is no racial bigotry here!
我這裏沒有種族歧視
I do not look down on niggers,kikes
我不鄙視黑鬼 猶太人
wops or greasers.
意大利人或墨西哥人
Here, you are all equally worthless!
你們在此同樣是廢物
My orders are to weed out non-hackers...
我奉命剔除無能者
...who do not pack the gear to be in my beloved Corps!
他們無法成為我所愛的...陸戰隊一份子
Do you maggots understand that?
你們是蛆蟲 明白嗎?
Bullshit! I can't hear you!
屁話 我聽不到
What's your name, scumbag?
你姓什麼? 人渣
Sir, Private Brown, sir!
長官 二等兵布朗
From now on you're Private Snowball!
以後你就叫"雪球"二等兵
Like that name?
喜歡這姓名嗎?
Sir, yes, sir!
長官 喜歡 長官
There's one thing you won't like!
但有一事你不會喜歡
They don't serve fried chicken and watermelon...
在我的廚房拉沒有...
...in my mess hall!
燒雞和西瓜...可以吃
Is that you, John Wayne?Is this me?
你或是約翰韋恩? 還是我?
Who said that?
誰說這話?
Who the fuck said that?
那個該死的說話?
Who's the slimy communist cocksucker down here...
誰是這排討厭的共黨份子...
...who just signed his own death warrant?
剛才是誰簽署了自己的死刑令?
Nobody, huh?
沒人承認嗎?
The fairy fucking godmother said it!
他的童話是該死的教母說的
Out-fucking-standing! I will P.T. you all until you die!
地地道道的狗屎! 我要你們不停地操練! 直到力竭而死為止
I will P.T. you until your assholes suck buttermilk!
我會你們不斷操練直到你的肛門可以吸奶
Was it you, you little fuck?
是不是你? 你個小雜種
You look like a fucking worm! I bet it was you!
你看起來就像是一個他媽的懦夫! 我敢打賭一定是你!
Sir, I said it, sir!
長官 是我說的 長官
Well, no shit.
好吧 不操你了
What are you, a fucking comedian? Private Joker.
你是該死的喜劇演員嗎? 二等兵小丑
I admire your honesty.
我很欣賞你的誠實
I like you. Come over to my house and fuck my sister!
我喜歡你 來 到我家泡我妹子吧
You little scumbag! I've got your name!
你個小渣滓 我已經知道到你的名字!
I've got your ass!
我能隨意支配你這頭蠢驢!
You will not laugh or cry!You will learn by the number!
你將會啼笑皆非! 你將會從頭學起!
Get up! Get on your feet!
站起來! 併攏你的腳!
Unfuck yourself or I'll unscrew your head
操你自己或讓我擰下你的腦袋...
and shit down your neck!
並且把大便放進你脖子裏
- Why did you join my beloved Corps? - Sir, to kill, sir!
- 為何加入我所愛的陸戰隊? - 長官 為了殺人!
You're a killer!
你是個殺手?
Let me see your war face!
讓我看看你的殺人表情
You've got a war face?
你有殺人表情嗎?
That's a war face! Let me see yours!
這有殺人表情? 讓我看看!
You didn't convince me! Let me see your real war face!
你沒有說服我! 讓我看你真正的殺人表情!
You don't scare me! Work on it!
你沒嚇怕我! 繼續做!
What's your excuse?
你對此有何辯解?
Sir, excuse, sir?
長官 辯解? 長官!
I'm asking the fucking questions,understand?
是在我問該死的問題 明白嗎?
Thank you!Can I be in charge for a while?
謝謝 我可否暫時負責一會兒?
Are you shook up? Nervous?
你感到震撼了嗎? 緊張嗎?
Sir, I am, sir!
長官 是的
Do I make you nervous?
我使你緊張不安嗎?
Were you about to call me an asshole?
你要稱我為笨蛋嗎?
How tall are you, Private?
你有多高? 二等兵
Sir, 5'9", sir!
長官 五尺九寸
I didn't know they stacked shit that high!
我不知道大便能堆積得如此之高!
Trying to squeeze an inch in on me, huh?
你試圖誇張地增高一英吋 嗯?
The best part of you ran down the crack of your mama's ass and ended up as a brown stain on the mattress!
你爸給你的精華從你媽的臀部流到床墊成為棕色污漬
Where in hell are you from?
你來自何處?
Texas
德州
Holy dogshit! Only steers and queers come from Texas, Private Cowboy!
噢 狗屎! 只有公牛和同性戀者來自德州 二等兵牛仔
You don't look like a steer,so that narrows it down!
你看起來不像公牛 因此定是同性戀!
Suck dicks?
你口交嗎?
You a peter-puffer?
你替男人口交服務嗎?
I bet you would fuck a person in the ass...
我敢打賭你一定和男人唱後庭花
...and not have the courtesy to give him a reach-around!
...但連替他自慰的禮貌也沒有
I'll be watching you!
我會注意你的!
Your parents have children that lived?
你父母還有活著子女的嗎?
Bet they regret that!
我打賭他們感到後悔!
You're so ugly you're a modern-art masterpiece!
你醜得像個現代藝術傑作
What's your name, fatbody?
你姓什麼? 肥仔!
Sir, Leonard Lawrence, sir!
長官 萊納勞倫斯長官
Lawrence, what, of Arabia?
勞倫斯 什麼 阿拉伯勞倫斯?
That name sounds like royalty!
這名字聽起來像王室
You royalty?
你是王室嗎?
You suck dicks?
你吸老二嗎?
Bet you could suck a golf ball through a garden hose!
你一定可透過吸管吸高爾夫球?
I don't like that name!
我不喜歡你這姓名
Faggots and sailors are called Lawrence!
同性戀和水手都姓勞倫斯
From now on you're Gomer Pyle!
從今起你是戈默派爾
Think I'm cute, Private Pyle?Think I'm funny?
覺得我很可愛嗎 二等兵派爾? 覺得我好笑嗎?
Then wipe off that disgusting grin!
那麼抹掉那討厭的微笑!
Any fucking time, sweetheart!
在任何該死的時間 甜心
I'm trying, sir!
我在努力
I'll give you three seconds...
我給你三秒鐘時間
...exactly three fucking seconds...
就他媽的三秒鐘時間
...to wipe off that stupid grin...
消除你那愚蠢的笑容
...or I will gouge out your eyeballs and skull-fuck you!
否則我會挖出你眼球與你的腦袋做愛
Sir, I can't help it, sir!
長官 我無法控制 長官
Get on your knees, scumbag!
讓你的膝蓋跪下 人渣
Now choke yourself!
現在窒息你自己
Goddamn it, with my hand, numb-nuts!
該死的 是用我的手 笨蛋!
Don't pull my hand over there!
不要把我的手拉向那裏!
I said choke yourself!Lean forward
我說窒息自己 頭伸前...
and choke yourself!
勒死你自己
Are you through grinning?
你微笑完了嗎?
Bullshit! I can't hear you!
屁話 我聽不到你
Bullshit! I still can't hear you!
屁話 我仍聽不到
Sound off like you got a pair!
像男子漢氣概般地回答
That's enough. Get on your feet!
夠了 站立起來
Pyle, square your ass away and
派爾 挺起你的屁股
start shitting me Tiffany cuff links...
準備給我排泄金袖扣
...or I will definitely fuck you up!
否則我一定會整慘你
Parris lsland, South Carolina ...
南卡洛萊納州巴里島
...the United States Marine Corps Recruit Depot.
美國海軍陸戰隊訓練中心
An eight-week college
接受為期八周的
for the phony-tough and the crazy-brave.
英勇和愚蠢大膽的訓練
Mama and Papa were laying in bed!
爸和媽躺在床上
Mama rolled over and this is what she said:
媽翻身過去說道...
Oh, give me some...
給我來些...
...P.T.!
體能訓練
Good for you and good for me!
體能對你 對我都有裨益
Mmm, good!
好
Up in the morning to the rising sun!
跟隨太陽東昇早起
Gotta run all day......till the running's done!
我們須整日跑步 直到奔跑結束
Ho Chi Minh is a son of a bitch!
胡志明是狗娘養的
Got the blueballs, crabs and the seven- year itch!"
染上性病陰虱癥 患七年之癢
Left shoulder, hut!
舉槍掛左肩
What are you trying to do to my beloved Corps?
你究竟想對我所愛的陸戰隊幹嘛?
Sir, I don't know, sir!
長官 我不知道
Do you expect me to believe that you don't know left from right?
你期望我相信你不知道怎麼辨別左右?
You did that on purpose!You want to be different!
你是故意如此 還是想要與眾不同?
What side was that?
這是哪一邊?
Sir, left side, sir!
長官 是左邊
Are you sure, Private Pyle?
你能確定嗎? 派爾
What side was that?
是左或右?
Sir, right side, sir!
長官 是右邊
Don't fuck with me again, Pyle!Pick up your fucking cover!
別再向我挑戰 拾起你的軍帽
Tonight, you pukes will sleep with your rifles!
今晚 你們將和你們的步槍同睡
You will give your rifle a girl's name!
你們要為步槍取個女孩名
Because this is the only pussy you people are going to get!
因為這是你們唯一可獲得的性伴侶
Your days of finger-banging old Mary Jane Rottencrotch...
你們用手指穿過異性粉紅內褲...
...through her pretty pink panties are over!
...摸索私處的日子已告結束
You're married to this piece...
你們已經和這個
...this weapon of iron and wood!
鐵與木做成的武器結婚
And you will be faithful!
你必須對它忠貞不二
Prepare to mount!
預...備!
Pray!
祈禱!
"This is my rifle.
這是我的步槍
There are many like it,but this one is mine.
尚有很多類似的步槍 但這支是我的
My rifle is my best friend.
我的步槍是我最好的朋友
It is my life.
這是我的生命
I must master it,as I must master my life.
我須支配步槍 像我支配我的生命般
Without me, my rifle is useless.
沒有我 我步槍等同於廢物
Without my rifle, I am useless.
沒有步槍 我也等同於廢人
I must fire my rifle true.
我必須準確開火
I must shoot straighter than my enemy,
我必須先射殺我的敵人
who is trying to kill me.
不然他就會殺死我
I must shoot him before he shoots me.
我一定要在敵人射殺我之前
I will.
先射殺他
Before God I swear this creed.
在上帝前我立下這個誓言!
My rifle and myself are defenders of my country.
我的步槍和我自己是我祖國的保衛者
We are the masters of our enemy.
我們是我們敵人的主人
We are the saviors of my life.
我們是我生命的救世主...
So be it......until there is no enemy, but peace.
直到沒有敵人 直到和平實現...
"Amen."
阿門!
At ease!
稍息!
Good night, ladies!
晚安 女士們
Hit it!
上床
This is not your daddy's shotgun,Cowboy!
這不是你爸的鳥槍 牛仔
Move the rifle around your head,not your head around the rifle!
將槍環繞你的頭 不是用頭環繞槍
Four inches from your chest, Pyle!
距離你的胸口四英吋 派爾!
Four inches!
4英吋!
"This is my rifle! This is my gun!
這是我的步槍!　這是我的老二!
"This is for fighting! This is for fun!
這是為了作戰! 這是為了享樂!
"This is my rifle! This is my gun!
這是我的步槍! 這是我的老二!
"This is for fighting!This is for fun! "
這是為了作戰! 這是為了享樂!
You're bouncing!
漆蓋抬起來!
Ten fucking seconds!
該死的十秒鐘
It should take you ten seconds to negotiate this obstacle!
你們應該在十秒內爬過這道障礙物
Quickly, move it out!
快點! 行動起來!
No swinging-dick private in this platoon's gonna graduate...
本排士兵在十秒內不能爬過障礙物...
...until they get this obstacle down to less than ten fucking seconds!
...就不能結束訓練
Get over that goddamn obstacle!Move it!Next two! Quickly!
下面二人 快點! 穿過那障礙物 趕快!
Private Joker, are you a killer?
二等兵小丑 你是殺手嗎?
Let me hear your war cry!
讓我聽聽你的戰鬥吼聲!
Get your fat ass over there!
把你的肥肉滾過去!
That's right, Private Pyle...
這才對 二等兵派爾
...don't make any fucking effort to get up to the top!
不要妄圖不作任何努力想從障礙物上面通過
If God wanted you up there,
如果上帝要你上去
He'd have miracled your ass up there!
它會顯現神跡使你上去
Get your fat ass up there!
把你的肥肉拿上去!
What the hell's wrong with you?
你有什麼問題嗎?
If there was some pussy up there,
要有女人的陰道在上面...
you could get up there, couldn't you?
你才能上去 是不是?
Your ass looks like about 150 pounds
你的肥臀看起來好像是150磅的...
of chewed bubble gum, Pyle.
嚼過的泡泡糖 派爾
One for the commandant!
一次向指揮官致敬!
One for the Corps!
一次向陸戰隊致敬!
Get up there!
用力拉高身體 上去
Pull!
用力!
The Corps don't get theirs!
你仍未替陸戰隊做一次
Get up there, Pyle!
上去 派爾
Pull!Pyle, pull!
用力拉高 派爾
One pull-up, Pyle! Come on, pull!
把身體拉高一些 用力拉
You've got to be shitting me! Get your ass up there!
你一定在開我玩笑 上去
Do you mean to tell me you cannot do one single pull-up?
難道你拉高一次也不行?
You are a worthless piece of shit, Pyle!Get out of my face!
你是廢物 派爾 走開
Get up there, Snowball.
上去 雪球
Get up here, fatboy!Quickly!
上去 胖子 快點爬上去
You climb obstacles like old people fuck.Do you know that, Private Pyle?
你爬越障礙象老年人做愛 你知道嗎? 派爾
Get up here! You're too slow! Move it!
爬上去 你太慢了 快點!
Private Pyle, whatever you do,don't fall down!
無論你幹什麼都不要下墜
That would break my fucking heart!
那會傷我他媽的心
Quickly! Up and over! Up and over!
快點 爬下去
What in the fuck are you waiting for,Private Pyle?
你在等什麼? 派爾
Get up and over!
爬到頂後爬下去
Move it, move it!
快點!
Are you quitting on me?
你就此放棄了?
Well, are you?
是不是?
Then quit, you slimy, fucking, walrus- looking piece of shit!
那麼放棄吧 你這矮胖的廢物
Get the fuck off of my obstacle!
離開我的障礙物
Now! Move it!
現在!快點!
I'm going to rip your balls off so you can't contaminate the rest of the world!
我要摘掉你的睪丸以免污染世界
I will motivate you, Private Pyle...
我會激勵你 二等兵派爾...
...if it short-dicks every cannibal on the Congo!
無論任務如何艱難
Pick 'em up and set 'em down, Pyle!
雙足踏地 派爾
Quickly! Move it up!
快點! 跑起來!
Were you born a fat, slimy scumbag,you piece of shit, Private Pyle?
你是一堆天生的肥肉 粘乎乎的渣滓 你是一馱大便嗎? 二等兵派爾?
Or did you have to work on it?
還是這就是你的工作?
Move it up!Quickly! Hustle up!
快點 迅速些
The fucking war will be over by the time we get out there, Private Pyle!
等我們開赴前線該死的越戰早已結束 二等兵派爾!
Are you going to fucking die?Are you going to die on me?
你他媽的要死嗎? 你馬上要死在我身上嗎?
Do it now!
快點啊!
Move it up!Hustle it up! Quickly!
快點 越快越好
Feel dizzy?
感到頭暈嗎?
Faint?
昏眩嗎?
Jesus H. Christ,I think you've got a hard- on!
天呀 你覺得你居然勃起了!
Quickly, ladies! Assholes and elbows!Move it out!
快點 女士們 擺動手肘 跑起來!
Get up!
快點 起來
Reveille! Reveille!
起床號 起床號
Drop your cocks and grab your socks!
停止自慰 快穿起你的襪子!
Today is Sunday!Divine worship is 0800.
今天是星期日 早晨八時聽講道
Get your bunks made and your uniforms on.
整理你的內務 穿上你的制服
Police call in two minutes.
二分鐘後檢查營房
Private Cowboy, Private Joker.
牛仔 小丑
Finish your bunks, then you two turds clean the head.
整理床位後你們二人去清洗廁所
I want that head so sanitary...
我要廁所乾淨得...
...that the Virgin Mary could go in there and take a dump!
連聖母瑪利亞也能樂意去如廁
Do you believe in the Virgin Mary?
你相信有聖母瑪利亞嗎?
Sir, no, sir!
長官 我不信
Private Joker, I don't believe I heard you correctly!
我沒有聽清楚 二等兵
Sir, the private said "No, sir," sir!
長官 二等兵說不信
You little maggot!You make me want to vomit!
你這小蛆蟲讓我嘔吐
You communist heathen
你這共黨異教徒...
sound off that you love the Virgin Mary...
大聲回答你愛聖母瑪利亞
...or I'll stomp your guts out!
不然我揍扁你!
You love the Virgin Mary, don't you?
你愛聖母瑪利亞 是嗎?
Negative, sir!
不 長官
Are you trying to offend me?
你想得罪我嗎?
Sir, the private believes that
長官 二等兵認為他任何的回答...
any answer he gives will be wrong!
都被當成錯誤
And that you will beat him harder
如果他否定了自己...
if he reverses himself, sir!
那你更會打他 長官!
Who's your squad leader?
誰是你的班長?
The private's squad leader is Private Snowball, sir!
二等兵班長是二等兵雪球
Private Snowball reporting, sir!
二等兵雪球報告 長官
You're fired! Private Joker is promoted to squad leader!
你已被革職 小丑提升為班長
Disappear, scumbag!
滾吧 人渣
Reporting as ordered, sir!
奉命報到 長官
From now on Private Joker is your new squad leader
小丑今後是你的新班長
and you bunk with him.
你和他分睡上下鋪
He'll teach you!
他會教會你一切
He'll teach you how to pee!
教你如何小便
Private Joker is ignorant but he's got guts
小丑雖然無知但是有膽量
and guts is enough.
有膽量已足夠
Now you ladies carry on.
女士們繼續工作
The bolt. The bolt goes in the receiver.
把槍栓放入彈藥容器
Operating rod handle.
操作桿柄 操作標尺
Operating rod guide.
操作桿指南
Right one over the left And the left one over the right.
左鞋帶穿過右鞋帶 右邊的穿過左邊的
Just throw your other leg over.
一條腿先跨過去
Pull the next one over and you're home free.
再跨過另一腿便成功了
Just throw it over.
把腿跨過去
That'a boy. Just set it down.
幹得好 放下雙腿
Congratulations, Leonard.
恭喜 萊納
You did it.
你成功了
Fold the blanket and sheet back together.
把毛毯和床單折疊後
Make a four-inch fold.
折成四英吋寬
Got it?
明白嗎?
You do it.
你試一下
Right shoulder, hut!
步槍掛右肩
Port, hut!
握槍在胸前
Order, hut!
槍垂直 槍托著地
Square these weapons away.
準備武器
The deadliest weapon in the world...
世界最致命的武器...
...is a Marine, and his rifle.
是陸戰隊士兵和他的步槍
It is your killer instinct that must be harnessed...
如果你們想在在戰鬥中生還
...if you expect to survive in combat.
必須利用你們的殺人本能
Your rifle...
步槍...
...is only a tool.
只是工具
It is a hard heart that kills.
冷酷的心才能殺人
If your killer instincts are not clean and strong...
若不清楚這些殺人的本能 不堅定
...you will hesitate at the moment of truth.
在生死關頭你們就會猶疑不決
You will not kill.
如果你們不願殺人
You will become dead Marines.
便會成為死的陸戰隊員
And then you will be in a world of shit.
你們就會有天大麻煩
Because Marines are not allowed...
因為陸戰隊員未經許可...
...to die without permission!Do you maggots understand?
不準死亡 你們這些蛆蟲明白嗎?
I love working for Uncle Sam!
我喜歡為美國工作
Lets me know just who I am!
讓我知道自己是誰
One, two, three, four!United States Marine Corps!
一 二 三 四 美國海軍陸戰隊
One, two, three, four!I love the Marine Corps!
一 二 三 四 我愛陸戰隊
My Corps! Your Corps!
我的 你們的陸戰隊
Our Corps! Marine Corps!
我們的 海軍陸戰隊
"I don't know, but I've been told...
我不知道 但據說...
...Eskimo pussy is mighty cold!
愛斯基摩女性的陰道很寒冷
Mmm, good! Feels good!
好 好感覺 好 好舒服
Is good! Real good!
好 真好
"Tastes good! Mighty good!
美味 十分可口
"Good for you! Good for me! "
對你有益 對我有益
Trim 'em!
剪指甲
Toe-jam!
腳趾甲太髒
Pop that blister!
把水泡割破
Jesus H. Christ!
我的天!
Why is your footlocker unlocked?
你的衣物箱為何不上鎖?
Sir, I don't know, sir!
長官 我不知道
If there is one thing in this world I hate...
這世上我最痛恨的...
...it is an unlocked footlocker!
就是沒上鎖的衣物箱
You know that, right?
你知道嗎?
Without dickheads like you,there'd be no thievery in the world!
沒有你這類蠢人世界上便沒有偷盜
Get down!
下來
Now let's just see if there's anything missing!
檢查是否有東西遺失
Holy Jesus!
天呀
What is that?
這是什麼?
What the fuck is that?
那是該死的什麼?
What is that, Private Pyle?
這是什麼? 派爾
Sir, a jelly doughnut, sir!
長官 果醬甜圈
Where did you get it?
何處得來的?
From the mess hall, sir!
廚房
Is chow allowed in the barracks, Pyle?
營房准許藏有食物嗎?
Are you allowed to eat jelly doughnuts, Private?
你獲准吃果醬甜圈嗎?
Why not, Private?
為何不准?
Sir, because I'm too heavy, sir!
長官 因為我的肥胖
Because you are a disgusting fatbody,Private Pyle!
因為你是個很討厭的肥豬 派爾
Then why did you hide a jelly doughnut in your footlocker?
你衣物箱為何藏有果醬甜圈
Because I was hungry, sir!
因為我很餓 長官
Because you were hungry?
因為你很餓?
Private Pyle...
二等兵派爾...
...has dishonored himself and dishonored the platoon!
使他自己和他所屬一排蒙受了恥辱
I have tried to help him,but I have failed!
我試圖幫助他 但失敗了
I have failed because you have not helped me!
我失敗是因為你們沒有幫助我
You people...
你們同僚之間...
...have not given Private Pyle the proper motivation!
沒有很好地激勵和督促他
From now on,whenever Private Pyle fucks up...
那麼 從今天起無論派爾犯什麼錯誤
...I will not punish him.
我不處罰他...
I will punish all of you!
我卻要處罰你們全體
And the way I see it, ladies...
女士們 在我看來
...you owe me for one jelly doughnut!
你們欠我一個果醬甜圈
Get on your faces!
面向地臥下
Open your mouth!
張開你的嘴
They're paying for it, you eat it!
他們因你受罰 你吃了它
Ready, exercise!
準備...操練
One, two, three, four!
一 二 三 四
"I love the Marine Corps! "
我愛海軍陸戰隊
One, two, three, four!I love the Marine Corps!
一 二 三 四 我愛海軍陸戰隊
You really look like shit today.
你今天的模樣的確很難看
Everybody hates me now.
現在人人都憎恨我
Even you.
連你也是
Nobody hates you, Leonard.
我沒有恨你 萊納
You just keep making mistakes,getting everybody in trouble.
你不斷犯錯 給大家惹麻煩
I can't do anything right.
我什麼也做不好
I need help.
我需要幫助
I'm trying to help you.
我試圖幫助你
I'm really trying.
我確實在努力嘗試
Tuck your shirt in.
把你的襯衫塞進褲子裏
Do it.
打他
Remember, it's just a bad dream, fatboy.
記住 這只是場惡夢 死胖子
Do we love our beloved Corps, ladies?
我們愛我們所愛的陸戰隊嗎?
Semper fi, do or die!Gung ho, gung ho!
永遠忠誠! 意志堅決! 同心協力!
What makes the grass grow?
什麼使青草生長?
Blood, blood, blood.
血! 血! 血!
What do we do for a living, ladies?
我們如何謀生? 女士們
Kill, kill, kill!
殺! 殺! 殺!
I can't hear you!
我聽不到你們
Kill, kill, kill!
殺! 殺! 殺!
Bullshit! I still can't hear you!
屁話 我仍聽不到你們
Kill, kill, kill!
殺! 殺! 殺!
Do any of you know who Charles Whitman was?
你們知道查理士 威曼是誰嗎?
None of you dumbasses knows?
你們笨得沒有一個人知道嗎?
Sir, he shot all those people
長官 他在德州奧斯汀市
from that tower in Austin, Texas, sir!
從塔中射擊多人
Charles Whitman killed 12 people...
查理士 威曼
...from a 28-story observation tower at the University of Texas...
在德州大學二十八層的...
...from distances of up to 400 yards.
瞭望塔 四百碼距離擊斃十二人
Anybody know who Lee Harvey Oswald was?
有人知道李哈納 奧斯華是誰?
Sir, he shot Kennedy, sir!
長官 他射殺了甘迺迪 長官
And do you know how far away he was?
你知道他距離目標有多遠?
Sir, it was far!
長官 很遠
From that book suppository building, sir!
他從藥館那射擊
Knock it off!
不准笑
250 feet!
是250英尺
He was 250 feet away and shooting at a moving target.
他自250英尺外射擊移動目標
He got off three rounds...
六秒內擊發三發子彈
...with an ltalian bolt-action rifle in six seconds...
用義肢操作彈匣的步槍
...and scored two hits,including a head shot!
二次擊中目標 包括頭部中彈
Do any of you know where these individuals learned to shoot?
誰知道這二人何處學習射擊?
Sir, in the Marines, sir!
長官 海軍陸戰隊
In the Marines! Outstanding!Those individuals...
陸戰隊 了不起 這些人...
...showed what one motivated Marine
用這樣的態度證明了...
and his rifle can do!
海軍陸戰隊的戰鬥力!
Before you ladies leave my island...
各位"女士"在離開我的島之前
...you will all be able to do the same thing!
你也具有同樣殺人威力
Happy birthday to you
生日快樂
"Happy birthday, dear Jesus"
生日快樂 親愛的耶穌
Today...
今天是...
...is Christmas!
聖誕節
There will be a magic show at 0930!
今晨九時半舉行假日布道
Chaplain Charlie will tell you...
查理牧師會告訴你們...
...about how the free world
自由世界將受到上帝和少數...
...with the aid of God and a few Marines!
陸戰隊員的幫助
will conquer Communism...
及如何征服共產主義
God has a hard-on for Marines...
上帝喜歡海軍陸戰隊
...because we kill everything we see!
因為我們催毀見到的任何東西
He plays His games...
上帝操縱人世間的大事
...we play ours!
我們玩我們的遊戲
To show our appreciation for so much power...
為了顯示我們感激如此的威力
...we keep heaven packed...
我們不停地使天堂...
...with fresh souls!
充滿新的靈魂
God was here before the Marine Corps!
上帝先於海軍陸戰隊來此
So you can give your heart to Jesus...
因為你仍可把心獻給耶穌
...but your ass belongs to the Corps!
但你們身體卻屬於陸戰隊所有
Do you ladies understand?
各位女士明白嗎?
I can't hear you!
我聽不到你們
It's been swabbed and brushed.
步槍已徹底擦試乾淨
Everything...
任何一切
...is clean.
都要乾淨清潔
Beautiful.
狀態一流
So that it slides perfectly.
槍機滑溜無阻
Nice.
很好
Everything cleaned...
一切已擦乾淨
...oiled.
加油
So that your action is beautiful.
因此 你行動美妙...
Smooth, Charlene.
光滑 莎蓮
Leonard talks to his rifle.
萊納對著步槍自言自語
I don't think Leonard can hack it anymore.
我想萊納不能再接受訓練
I think Leonard's a Section 8.
他應藉由精神問題退役
It don't surprise me.
我不感到驚訝
I want to slip my tubesteak into your sister.
我願和你姐妹做愛
What will you take in trade?
你要用什麼作交換?
What do you got?
你擁有什麼?
Outstanding!We've finally found something you do well!
你很卓越傑出 看來終於發現你的優點了
What is your 6th general order?
哨兵守則第六條是什麼?
Sir, to receive, obey and pass on
長官 把所有收到的命令遵守後
to the sentry who relieves me...
全部傳交於...
...all orders....
接替我的哨兵
Sir, the 6th general....
長官 第六條...
The private does not know, sir!
二等兵不知道 長官
You slimy scumbag,
你這可惡的混蛋
get down and give me 25!
做二十五次俯地挺身
How many counts in that movement?
那動作有多少拍?
Sir, four, sir!
長官 四拍
Why look down in the chamber?
為何觀察彈膛?
Sir, to be sure the inspecting officer is not given a loaded weapon, sir!
確保沒裝子彈將步槍呈送檢閱處
What's your 5th general order?
守則第五條是什麼?
Sir, to quit my post only when properly relieved, sir!
有哨兵接替我才能撤離崗位
What's this weapon's name?
這步槍叫什麼名字?
Sir, the private's weapon's name is Charlene, sir!
二等兵武器名叫莎蓮
Private, you are definitely born again hard.
二等兵 你的確變成勇悍的戰士了
I may even let you serve as a rifleman
我或許會讓你在我所愛的...
in my beloved Corps.
...陸戰隊當步兵
I don't want no teenage queen!
我不要青春皇后
I just want my M-14!
我只要我的M14步槍
If I die in the combat zone
如果我在戰場捐軀
Box me up and ship me home!
把我裝棺送回家鄉
Pin my medals upon my chest!
在我胸前別上勳章
"Tell my mom I've done my best! "
告訴我媽我已盡我所能
Graduation is only a few days away...
我們數日後結訓
...and the recruits of Platoon 3092 are salty.
3092排新兵勇悍善戰
They are ready to eat their own guts
他們有勇氣吃自己內臟...
and ask for seconds.
且要求添食
The instructors are proud to...
教官們以我們的進度...
...see us growing beyond their control.
超越他們的標準為榮
The Marine Corps does not want robots.
陸戰隊不需要機器人
The Marine Corps wants killers.
陸戰隊需要殺人戰士
The Marine Corps wants to build indestructible men.
陸戰隊需要製造不可毀滅的人
Men without fear.
無所畏懼的士兵
Today...
今天...
...you people are no longer maggots.
你們這些人不再是蛆蟲
Today, you are Marines.
今天 你們是陸戰隊士兵
You are part of a brotherhood.
你們情如兄弟
From now on, until the day you die...
從今天起直到你死的那天為止
... wherever you are...
無論你們身在何處 每一名陸戰隊員...
...every Marine is your brother.
都是你們的兄弟
Most of you will go to Vietnam.
你們多數人將前往越南
Some of you will not come back.
你們有些將不會再回來
But always remember this:
但永遠記住這一點...
Marines die.
陸戰隊士兵會有犧牲...
That's what we're here for!
那是我們作戰之目的
But the Marine Corps lives forever.
但海軍陸戰隊將永存不朽!
And that means you live forever!
那表示你們也將永遠存在
0300, Infantry.
0300步兵
1800, Engineers.
1800工兵
You go out and find mines.Cowboy!
你探測地雷 牛仔
0300, Infantry.
0300步兵
Joker!4212
小丑 4212
...Basic Military Journalism.
基本軍事新聞工作
You must be shitting me!
你一定在開我玩笑
You think you're Mickey Spillane?You think you're some kind of fucking writer?
你以為自己是他媽的作家?
Sir, I wrote for my high- school newspaper, sir!
長官 我為中學報章寫作過
Christ, you're not a writer,you're a killer!
你不是什麼狗屁作家而是殺手
A killer, yes, sir!
是 長官
Gomer Pyle!
戈默 派爾
You forget your fucking name? 0300
你忘了自己姓名嗎? 0300
Infantry. You made it.
步兵 你成功了
Our last night on the island.
我們在巴里島的最後一晚
I draw fire watch.
我奉命擔任守衛
Hi, Joker.
小丑 你好
Are those...
這些是...
...live rounds?
實彈嗎?
7.62 millimeter.
七點六二毫米口徑
Full metal jacket.
銅質彈殼子彈
Leonard, if Hartman comes in here and catches us...
萊納 如果被哈曼進來發覺的話...
...we'll both be in a world of shit.
我們會有天大的麻煩
I am...
我已有...
...in a world...
麻煩...
...of shit!
干!
Left shoulder, hut!
左肩
Right shoulder, hut!
右肩
Lock and load.
裝彈準備
Order, hut!
槍托垂地
"This is my rifle!
這是我的步槍
"There are many like it,but this one is mine."
有很多類似的步槍 但這枝是我的
Get back in your bunks!
回到你們床鋪去
What is this Mickey Mouse shit?
鬧什麼狗屎米老鼠?
What in the name of Jesus H. Christ are you animals doing in my head?
你們這些動物在我的廁所幹什麼?
Why is Pyle out of his bunk after lights out?
派爾為何在熄燈後離開他的床鋪?
Why is Pyle holding that weapon?
派爾為何拿著那武器?
Why aren't you stomping Private Pyle's guts out?
你難道沒膽打得他頭破額裂嗎?
Sir, it is the private's duty to inform you...
長官 我有責任告知你...
...that Private Pyle has a full magazine and has locked and loaded, sir!
二等兵派爾的步槍已裝實彈隨時可以射擊
Now listen to me, Private Pyle...
現在聽我說 派爾
...and listen good.
小心聽著
I want that weapon...
我想要那武器
..and I want it now!
現在就給我
Place that rifle on the deck at your feet...
把步槍放在你腳邊的地上
...and step back away from it.
然後退後一步離開它
What is your major malfunction,numb-nuts?
你精神是否有問題? 笨蛋
Didn't Mommy and Daddy show you...
難道幼年時你爸媽...
...enough attention when you were a child?
沒有足夠關懷你嗎?
Easy, Leonard.
冷靜點 萊納
Go easy, man.
冷靜點 夥計
Hey, baby.You got girlfriend Vietnam?
寶貝 你有越南女友嗎?
Not just this minute.
暫時沒有
Well, baby, me so horny.
寶貝 慾火旺盛
Me so horny.
我情慾高漲
Me love you long time.
我和你長時間做愛
You party?
你願做愛嗎?
Yeah, we might party.
好啊 我們或許會
How much?
多少錢?
$15.
十五美元
$15 for both of us?
我們兩人十五元
No. Each you $15.
不 每人十五元
Me love you long time.
我和你長時間做愛
Me so horny.
慾火焚身
$15 too beaucoup.
十五元太貴
$5 each.
每人五元
Me suckee-suckee.
我吸老二 吸老二
Me love you too much.
和你熱烈做愛
$5 is all my mom allows me to spend.
五元吧 我媽媽只准我花這點錢
Okay!
好吧
$10 each.
每人十元
What do we get for $10?
十元能得到什麼服務?
Everything you want.
一切你想要的
Everything?
所有一切?
Buddy
老友
you feel like spending some of your hard-earned money?
你願意浪費些血汗錢嗎?
Half of these gook whores are officers in the Viet Cong.
這些越南妓女一半以上供給越共軍官
The other half have TB.
另外一半已感染結核病
Be sure you only fuck the ones who cough.
也許 你只是想和結核病患者做愛
That sucker really had some moves on him.
那小賊功夫不錯
You know what pisses me off about these people?
你知道我為何對越南人感到憤怒?
WHY?
為什麼?
We're helping them and they shit all over us.
我們正在幫助他們 他們卻愚弄我們
I just can't feature that.
我簡直不明白
Don't take it too hard.
不這麼做太難了
It's just business.
這只是職責
I hate Da Nang.
我討厭惡峴港
I want to go out into the field.
我只想上前線
I'm here three months and all I do is...
我來這裏3個月了 只是拍攝那些...
...take handshake shots at award ceremonies.
...授勳儀式中的握手照
You'd get wasted the first day
若你上戰場的第一天就被殺...
and it would be my fault.
那將是我的錯
A high-school girl could do my job.
中學女生就可勝任我的工作
I want to get into the shit.I want some trigger time.
我想要投身到炮火連天的戰場中
If you get killed...
你若死了...
your mom will find me and beat the shit out of me.
你媽媽準會找到我後把我痛打一頓
That's a negative.
你的請求負面影響太大
Let's keep it short and sweet.
讓我們盡量簡短扼要
Anybody got anything new?
你們有得到什麼新報導嗎?
Rumor has it that the Tet ceasefire will be cancelled.
傳聞農曆新年停火協議將被取消
Rear echelon paranoia.
後方指揮部神經過敏
Intelligence says Charlie...
有情報說 越共在農曆新年...
...might try something big during Tet.
可能會有大攻勢
They say the same thing every year.
他們每年都這麼說
There's a lot of talk about it.
這類傳聞有很多
Don't lose any sleep over it.
別因此而擔心
The Tet holiday is like July Fourth
農曆新年相當於美國國慶日
Christmas and New Year in one.
聖誕與新年一樣
Every zipperhead in the North and South,will bang gongs...
每一個越南人在他們的新年...
...and bark at the moon.
都會大肆隆重慶祝
Ann- Margret and entourage are due next week.
安 瑪格莉慰問團將於下周抵達
I want someone to stick with her for a few days.
我想有人要堅持陪同她幾天
Rafterman, you take it.
賴特曼 你來擔任
Get some good low-angle stuff.
拍些精彩的低角度照片
Don't be obvious
別拍得太露骨
but I want to see fur and early morning dew.
但我想看到皮草及晨露
"Diplomats in Dungarees. Marine engineers
外交家 海軍陸戰隊工兵...
...rebuild Dong Phuc villages...."
將會重建"同菲"村
Chili, if we move Vietnamese
辣椒 如果我們是越南人...
they are evacuees.
他們都將被撤離
If they come to us to be evacuated,they are refugees.
如果他們來了 我們可能無法撤離 他們是難民
I'll make a note of it, sir.
我會注意這點的 長官!
"N.V.A. Soldier Deserts After Reading Pamphlets."
北越士兵閱讀小冊後將叛離...
""An N.V.A. regular, who realized deserted after reading Open Arms pamphlets."
北越正規軍閱讀"歡迎投城"小冊後...
his side would lose...
...將失敗而投城
That's good, Dave.
寫得不錯 戴夫
But why say, "N.V.A. regular"?
但為什麼用 "北越正規軍" ?
Is there an irregular?How about N.V.A. soldier?
有非正規軍嗎? 用"北越士兵"怎麼樣?
I'll fix it.
我會修改的
"The Lawrence Welk Show" will be on TV in two weeks.
"勞倫斯 威恩秀"將在兩周內上電視
Dave, do 100 words on it.
戴夫 寫篇100字的報導
"Not While We're Eating."
"我們在吃飯時停火"
"N.V.A. learned not to interrupt meals of Marines on a search-and-destroy mission."
N V A (北越軍)懂得了不去打擾正在執行"搜索和摧毀"任務士兵們的用餐
We have a new directive from M.A.F. on search and destroy.
我們有了一個新的命令: M A F 意為"搜索和摧毀"
Substitute "sweep and clear"in place of "search and destroy."
用"打掃及清理"代替"搜索和摧毀"
Got it?
明白嗎?
Got it.
明白了
Very catchy.
非常醒目
And, Joker
那麼 小丑
where's the weenie?
要點在哪裏?
The kill.
殺敵!
The grunts must have hit something.
描寫陸戰隊殺死一些敵軍
Didn't see them.
我沒有看到他們(指敵軍屍體)
I've told you,we run two basic stories here.
我已經告訴過你了 我們刊登了兩種基本的報導
Grunts who buy toothbrushes and deodorant for gooks:
一種是描寫陸戰隊購買牙刷和除臭劑贈予越南人民:
"Winning of Hearts And Minds."
"獲取好感和民心"
And combat action resulting in a kill: "Winning the War."
另一種是作戰行動的後果導致了這樣的報導: "贏得這場戰爭的勝利"
You must have seen blood trails,
你沒有看到血腥的道路...
drag marks?
或拖屍的痕跡?
It was raining
當時在下雨
sir.
長官
That's why God passed the law of probability.
這也就是為什麼上帝要制訂或然率
Rewrite it with a happy ending,say, one kill.
把它改寫成一個愉快的結局 也就是說 殺個人
A sapper or an officer. Which?
工兵或軍官? 到底用哪一個?
Whichever you say.
隨你喜歡...
Grunts like reading about dead officers.
陸戰隊員喜歡讀一些敵方軍官死亡的報導
Okay
好吧
an officer. How about a general?
一名軍官怎麼樣?
You'd like our guys to read the paper and feel bad?
你難道喜歡我們的讀者看到"星條旗報"而難過?
In case you didn't know, this is not a popular war.
萬一你不知道 這並不是一個受歡迎的戰爭
Our job is to report the news that the...
我們的工作就是在報導中又傳來了...
..."why-are-we-here" civilian newsmen ignore.
"為什麼-是-我們-這裏" 等民報記者忽視的問題
Maybe you should go out on some ops yourself.
或許你該親自上幾次前線
You could find more blood trails
你可發現更多的"血漬"
and drag marks.
和"拖屍的痕跡"
I've had my ass in the grass.
我曾經身臨戰場
Can't say I liked it much.
並不是說我喜歡這樣
Lots of bugs and too dangerous.
因為那兒有大量的臭蟲並且很危險
My present duties keep me where I belong:
我現在因職務纏身不能離此地 我是屬於...
In the rear with the gear.
...後方的補給品
Tet.
農曆新年
The Year of the Monkey.
猴年
Vietnamese Lunar New Year's Eve.
越南農曆新年的除夕夜
Down in Dogpatch, the gooks are shooting off fireworks to celebrate.
越南人民會燃放煙花爆竹來慶祝
I am fucking bored to death, man.
我都快被憋死了
I have to get back in the shit.
我必須上前線
I ain't heard a shot fired in anger in weeks.
我幾周都沒有聽到槍炮聲了
Joker's so tough, he'd eat the boogersout of a dead man's nose...
小丑很大膽 他敢吃死人的鼻屎
...then ask for seconds.
還嚷著要添食
Listen up, pilgrim.
聽著 漫遊者
A day without blood is like day without sunshine!
一天不見血就像是一天看不到太陽
Joker thinks the bad bush is
小丑認為戰爭危險 還是...
between old mama-san's legs.
女人的兩腿之間危險
He's never been in the shit.
他從未經歷炮火連天
Hard to talk about.
難以形容戰況
Like on Hastings.
像我親歷海斯丁之役
You weren't on Operation Hastings.
你沒參與該役
You weren't even in country.
你那時甚至還沒來越南
Eat shit and die, you fucking
去你的
Spanish-American poge!
去吃屎吧 你這該死的反戰的西班牙裔
I was there! I was in the shit with the grunts.
我當時就在那兒! 我確實和陸戰隊參加過那次酷戰
Don't listen to Payback's bullshit
別聽裘白克的屁話
Rafterman.
賴特曼
Sometimes he thinks he's John Wayne.
他有時以為自己是約翰韋恩
You listen to Joker.
你們聽聽小丑怎麼說
He knows it very little.
他知道的很少
He's never been in the shit
他從來沒有上過戰場
'cause he ain't got the stare.
因此他缺少這種白眼瞪!
The 1,000-yard stare.
那是一千碼的瞪視
A Marine gets it after he's been in the shit too long.
只有久經沙場的陸戰隊員才會有這種瞪視
It's like, it's like you've really seen beyond.
好像...好像你真的看到過似的
I got it.All field Marines got it.
我和戰場上的陸戰隊員都有這種瞪視
And you'll have it, too.
他也會有
I will?
我會有嗎?
How do you stop five blacks
你怎麼阻止五個黑人...
from raping a white chick?
去強姦白人小妞
Fuck you.
去你的
Throw them a basketball.
拋一個籃球給他們
Incoming.
是敵軍炮火
They're outgoing!
是我軍炮火
That ain't outgoing!
不是我軍炮火
That ain't outgoing!Now what'd I just say?
我軍沒還擊 我剛才說什麼?
I hope they're just fucking with us.
希望越共不打神經戰
I ain't ready for this shit.
我還沒有做好戰鬥的心理準備
Cease fire!
停止射擊!
The enemy...
敵軍...
...has very deceitfully...
欺詐性地...
...taken advantage of the ceasefire...
...利用新年停火協議...
...to launch an offensive all over the country.
在整個越南發動攻勢
So far, we've had it pretty easy here.
迄今為止這基地還沒有受到猛烈攻擊
But we seem to be the exception.
這裏好像只是個例外!
Charlie has hit every military target in Vietnam and hit them hard.
越共向越南每一軍事目標發動猛烈攻擊
In Saigon...
在西貢市...
...the United States Embassy has been overrun by suicide squads.
美國大使館遭越共敢死隊蹂躪
Khe Sanh is standing by to be overrun.
溪山也有被攻陷的威脅
We have reports that a division of N.V.A....
我們獲悉北越軍一師...
...has occupied all of the city of Hue south of the Perfume River.
全部佔領香河南邊的順化市
In strategic terms,
以戰略而言 北越已經將...
Charlie's cut the country in half...
整個越南一分為二
...the civilian press are wetting their pants...
美國民間報章大起恐慌
...and even Cronkite is going to say
甚至連著名電視記者克隆凱特...
the war is now unwinnable.
也聲稱越戰輸定了
In other words...
換句話說...
...it's a huge shit sandwich
現在的形勢猶如我們必須去...
and we all have to take a bite.
...咬一口大便三明治
Does this mean Ann-Margret's not coming?
那表示安瑪格莉不來了嗎?
You go straight up to Phu Bai.
你立刻趕去富巴市
Captain January will need you.
詹瑞上尉需要你
And you take off that damn button.
你必須除下那該死的圓形徽章
You can't get killed wearing a peace symbol.
你不能佩戴著和平標誌被殺
Permission to go with Joker.
請批准我和小丑同行
Granted.
請求已批准
Sir
長官
permission not to take Rafterman.
我不想賴特曼和我同去
You still here?
你是說這兒嗎?
Vanish ricky-tick and take Rafterman with you.
立刻帶賴特曼啟程
You're responsible for him.
你必須負責照顧他
Get some! Get some!
殺死這些敵軍
baby!
寶貝
I've got you
我已擊敗你
mother!
渾蛋
Anyone who runs is a VC.
誰企圖逃跑便是越共
Anyone who stands still...
誰屹立不動...
...is a well-disciplined VC.
...是訓練精良的越共
You guys ought to do a story about me.
你們該寫文章報導我
Why should we do a story about you?
我們為何報導你?
'Cause I'm so fucking good!
因我擅長殺越共
That ain't no shit neither.
那也不是謊言
I've done got me 157 dead gooks killed.
我已殺死一百五十七名越南人
And 50 water buffaloes, too.
殺了五十頭水牛
Them are all certified.
全部已獲證實
Any women or children?
你曾殺婦孺嗎?
Sometimes.
有時候
How can you kill women and children?
你怎可殺婦女兒童?
Easy.
易如反掌
You just don't lead them so much.
別射向目標前面
Ain't war hell?
戰爭豈不可怕?
We want to get in the shit.
我們自願上前線
Down the road.
向前
Two-five.
五團二營
Outstanding!
好極了
Thanks.
謝謝
We're looking for First Platoon,Hotel two-five.
我們找五團二營第一排
I got a bro named Cowboy.
我有好友牛仔
You people one-one?
你們屬一團一營?
No, sir. We're reporters for "Stars and Stripes."
我們是星條旗報記者
I'm Cowboy's platoon commander.
我是牛仔的排長
He's just down the road in the platoon area.
他就在前面路那一排
May we tag along, sir?
我們可否同行?
No problem.
沒有問題
Welcome aboard.
歡迎加入
I'm Schinoski. Walter J. Schinoski.
我是華特辛諾斯基
They call me Mr. Touchdown.
他們稱我底線得分
I played ball for Notre Dame.
我是聖母大學足球隊員
You here to make Cowboy famous?
你來使牛仔成名?
Never happen, sir.
永遠不會 長官
If you came looking for a story,
如果你來找尋新聞
this is your lucky day.
今天是你幸運日
We got Condition Red
我們正處高度戒備...
and we expect rain.
期望猛戰
Outstanding.
好極了
We taking care of business?
我軍已有對策?
The N.V.A. are dug in deep.
北越軍備妥固守
Hotel Company is working this side of the river, house by house.
我軍在河這邊逐屋搜索敵人
Charles has his shit together,
北越軍頑強防守
but we're still getting some decent kills.
但我軍仍有收穫
We heard the N.V.A. executed a lot of gook civilians.
聽說北越軍處死大量平民
Affirmative.
確有其事
I saw bodies half a klick this side of the canal.
我在運河這邊半公里見有屍體
Can you show me where?
你能指示所在嗎?
The dead have been covered with lime.
屍體已被石灰掩蓋
The dead know only one thing:
死者只知一事
It is better to be alive.
活著比較好些
I make it 20.
我點數二十具
Is that the official body count, sir?
這是官方數字?
What outfit are you with?
你屬那部隊?
We're from "Stars and Stripes."
星條旗軍報記者
I'm Sergeant Joker
我是小丑中士
and this photographer is Rafterman.
攝影師賴特曼
I'm Lt. Cleves. Hartford.
我是克萊夫少尉
Connecticut
康乃迪克人
Have you got a body count, sir?
你有整體數目嗎?
Twenty.
二十具屍首
How did it happen, sir?
慘劇如何發生?
The N.V.A. came in with a list of gook names:
越共帶來一紙越南人名單
Government officials, policemen,
包括政府官員 警察
ARVN officers, teachers.
南越軍官和教師等
They asked them, real polite
越共禮貌地請他們次日來
to report the next day for political re-education.
受政治再教育
Everybody who turned up got shot.
凡報到者皆被槍殺
Some they buried alive.
有些人更遭活埋
What is that button on your body armor?
你防彈衣上什麼徽章?
A peace symbol, sir.
和平象徵 長官
Where did you get it?
那裏得來的?
I don't remember, sir.
我記不起
What is written on your helmet?
你頭盔寫有什麼?
"Born to Kill," sir.
"天生殺人"
You put "Born to Kill" on your helmet
頭盔寫"天生殺人"...
and wear a peace button.
戴和平章
Is that some kind of sick joke?
是否病態的開玩笑?
Well, what does it mean?
什麼意思?
I don't know, sir.
我不知道 長官
You don't know very much.
你不知道的很多
Get your head and your ass wired together or I will shit on you!
你頭腦要清醒些否則有麻煩
Answer my question or you'll stand tall before the Man.
答覆我問題否則遭紀律處分
I was referring to the duality of man
我意指人類二重性
sir.
長官
The duality of man.
人類二重性
The Jungian thing, sir.
卡爾容理論
Whose side are you on?
你支持美國或北越?
Our side, sir.
我們美國
Don't you love your country?
你不愛自己國家?
Yes, sir.
我愛國
Then get with the program. Jump on the team and come in for the big win.
那麼支持美國努力作戰取勝
I ask that my Marines obey my orders
我要求陸戰隊像聽從上帝般...
as they would the word of God.
服從我命令
We are helping the Vietnamese,because inside every gook...
我們正幫助越南人 因每一...
...is an American trying to get out.
越南人心中都願做美國人
It's a hardball world, son.
這是個危險世界 孩子
We must keep our heads
我們須保持冷靜直到...
until this peace craze blows over.
瘋狂和平運動消散
We're looking for First Platoon,Hotel two-five.
我們找尋第五團二營一排
Around the back.
就在後面
First Platoon?
第一排在哪裏?
Through there.
從那裏通過
Hey, Lone Ranger.
喂! 獨行俠
Holy shit!
令人驚喜
I hoped I'd never see you again,
希望永不再見到你
you piece of shit!
你這渾蛋
What's happening?
近況怎樣?
Just waiting to get back to the land of the big PX.
正等待回美國去
Here or there, samey-same.Why go back?
為何回國? 這裏那裏都一樣
Been getting any?
可有尋歡?
Only your sister.
只和你妹
Better my sister than my mom
和我妹好過我媽
though my mom's not bad.
但我媽不錯
Hey, you hogs
你們色情豬玀
listen up!
聽著
This is my bro, Joker
這是我好友小丑
from the island
巴里島同僚
And this is....
這位是...
They're from "Stars and Stripes."
他們是星條旗報記者
You'll be famous.
你們將會成名
We're the Lusthog squad.
我們色情豬班
We're lifetakers and heartbreakers.
我們殺人也傷人心
We shoot holes in them and fill them with lead.
我們專射殺越共
Are you a photographer?
你是攝影記者嗎?
I'm a combat correspondent.
不 我是戰地記者
You seen much combat?
你見過很多戰役嗎?
I've seen a little on TV.
我在電視看到一些
You're a real comedian.
你真是個滑稽客
Well, they call me the Joker.
他們稱我小丑
Well, I've got a joke for you.
我有個笑話給你
I'm going to tear you a new asshole.
我要扯裂你肛門給你新的
Well, pilgrim...
漫遊者
...only after you eat the peanuts out of my shit!
除非你能在我大便中吃花生
You talk the talk.
你口氣強硬
Do you walk the walk?
或你只動口不動手?
You might not believe it...
你或許不會相信...
...but under fire, Animal Mother is a truly fine human being.
野獸大致上是優秀的戰士
He just needs grenades thrown at him the rest of his life.
他一生只需有人向他投手榴彈
Jungle bunny.
黑鬼
Thank God for the sickle cell, huh?
多謝上帝患鏈形血球癥
Yeah, Mother.
對了 畜生
Hey, photographer!
喂! 攝影師
Want to take a good picture?
拍攝精彩照片嗎?
Take this.
拍攝他
This...is my bro.
這是我好友
This is his party.
這是他的宴會
He's the guest of honor.
他是宴會貴賓
Today is his birthday.
今天是他生日
Happy birthday, zipperhead!
生日快樂 笨蛋
I will never forget this day.
我永不忘今日
The day I came to Hue city and fought one million N.V.A. gooks.
今天我來順化和百萬越共作戰
I really love the little Commie bastards.
我確愛那共黨小雜種
These enemy grunts are as hard
這些敵軍像斜眼的...
as slant-eyed drill instructors.
教育班長那般強悍
These are great days we're living!
我們生活在偉大時代中
We are jolly green giants,
我們是強大巨人
walking the earth with guns.
全身武裝漫步地球
These people we wasted here today...
我們今天殺死的這些人
...are the finest people we will ever know.
將是我們所知最優秀的人類
Once we rotate back to the world,
我們一旦返美國後
we'll miss not having anyone worth shooting.
將無人值得我們射擊
Delta 6 Actual, this is Murphy. Over.
三角洲六 這是墨菲 通話
We are receiving incoming fire from the ville.
我們遭村落炮火轟擊
The lieutenant is down.
少尉已死
We'll stop and check out what's in front of us.
我們暫停 偵查前面情況
Okay, Lusthog squad, listen up!
好吧 色情豬班 聽著
We'll move up these two roads.
我們沿此兩條路前進
I want the third team up this road.
第三隊在這路上
First and second team behind me up this other road.
其他一路第一第二隊跟隨我後
Let's go! Let's get it done!
我們開始行動 走吧
Is that you, John Wayne? Is this me?
是你嗎? 約翰韋恩? 這是我
Start the cameras.This is "Vietnam: The Movie"!
搖動攝影機 是越南 電影
If Joker is John Wayne, I'm a horse!
小丑若是約翰韋恩 我就是馬
T.H.E. Rock can be a rock!
"貓竊賊"電視劇可能是岩石
I'll be Ann-Margret!
我將是安瑪格莉
Animal Mother can be a rabid buffalo!
畜生渾蛋可能患水牛病
I'll be General Custer!
我將是卡斯楚將軍
Who'll be the Indian?
誰是印地安人?
We'll let the gooks play the Indians!
我們讓越南人演印地安人
You're going home now.
你們現在回家去了
Semper fi.
永遠忠誠
We're mean Marines, sir.
我們是兇殘陸戰隊 長官
Go easy, bros.
安心去吧
Better you than me.
你們喪生好過我死
At least they died for a good cause.
至少他們有好理由捐軀
What cause was that?
什麼理由?
Freedom.
自由
Flush out your head gear, New Guy.
頭腦清醒些 菜鳥
You think we waste gooks for freedom?
你想我們為自由而殺越南人
This is a slaughter.
這越戰簡直是屠殺
If I get my balls blown off for a word...
如我因一字連睪丸都被炸去
...my word is "poontang."
這字就是陰道
Tough break for Hand Job.
自慰真不幸
He was set to get shipped out on a medical.
他本可因醫療退役送回國
What was wrong with him?
他健康有何不妥?
He was jerking off ten times a day.
他每天自慰十次
It's no shit. At least ten times a day.
真的 他至少每天十次
Last week he was sent to Da Nang to see the Navy head shrinker.
上周他奉命去峴港受精神治療
The crazy fucker jerks off in the waiting room.
那瘋狂呆子竟在候診室自慰
Instant Section 8.
因精神問題須立刻退役
He was waiting for his papers to clear division.
他正等待上級師部批准
Ready?
準備好嗎?
Turnover.
準備拍攝
Hue city interviews. Roll 34.
訪問順化市 第三十四景
This is a major city,so we have to assault with...
這是大城市 因此我軍須動用
They send us in first squad...tanks in the streets.
坦克在街道進攻 我們第一隊
...to make sure there are no little, uh...Vietnamese waiting with B-40 rockets
攻入市區確保沒有北越火箭炮
to blow the tanks away.
轟毀我軍坦克
So we roll the tanks in and basically,
我軍坦克進城
blow the place to hell.
基本上毀滅全市
When we're in Hue, in Hue city...
我們進入順化市
...it's like a war, you know.
整個城市好像戰場一般
Like what I thought about, what l thought a war was supposed to be.
就像我想像中的戰爭那樣
There's the enemy, kill them.
如發現敵軍 殺死他們
There's no question about it. We're the best.
毫無疑問陸戰隊最佳
It's bullshit about Air Cav.
陸軍空中騎兵師徒具虛名
When the shit hits the fan, who do they call?
戰局危急他們...
They call Mother Green
只得向陸戰隊求助
Do I think America belongs in Vietnam?
我認為美軍該在越南作戰?
I don't know. I belong in Vietnam,I'll tell you that.
我不知 只知我該在越南作戰
Can I quote L.B.J.?
我可否引述詹森總統嗎?
I will not send...
我不願派遣...
...American boys 10,000 miles around the world...
美國男孩遠赴一萬哩外...
...to do a job Asian boys
去做該由亞洲男孩自己...
should be doing for themselves
去做的工作
Personally, I think...
我個人認為
...they don't want to be involved in this war.
越南人不願捲入戰爭中
I think they sort of... took away our freedom and gave it
他們取走我們的自由
to the gooks. They don't want it.
贈與越南人 他們卻不要自由
They'd rather be alive than free.
他們認為活命好過自由
Poor dumb bastards.
可憐愚蠢雜種
The ones I'm fighting at are some pretty...
我的對手越共軍
...pretty bad boys. I'm not real, uh....
相當驍勇善戰
I'm not real keen on...
我對同一戰線的...
...these fellows that are supposedly on our side.
許多南越軍很不滿意
I keep meeting them coming the other way.
我發現他們臨陣退縮
We get killed for these people
我們為越南人民戰死
and they don't even appreciate it.
但他們毫無感激
They think it's a big joke.
他們認為天大笑話
If you ask me...
如你問我的話
...we're shooting the wrong gooks.
我們選錯敵軍作戰
It depends. I'm here
須看情況
to take combat photos.
我工作屬拍攝戰場照片
But if the shit gets too thick,I'll go to the rifle.
如戰況危急我會持槍作戰
What do I think of America's involvement in the war?
我對美國牽涉越戰看法?
I think we should win.
我認為我們該獲勝
I hate Vietnam.
我厭惡越南
There's not one horse in the whole country.
全國沒有一匹馬
There's something wrong with that.
這分明有些不妥
If they'd send us more guys maybe...
如果美國曾派援軍
...and bomb the hell out of the North,they might give up.
猛烈轟炸北越 北越可能投降
I wanted to see exotic Vietnam...
我要看到異國情調越南
...the jewel of Southeast Asia.
東南亞之寶石
I wanted to meet...
我願認識
...interesting people of an ancient culture and kill them.
古老文化有趣人物殺死他們
I wanted to be the first kid on my block
我要做我家街上第一個
to get a confirmed kill.
殺敵軍獲證實的孩子
'Morning, little schoolgirl.
早安 小女學生
I'm a little schoolboy, too.
我也是小男學生
What you got there?
你有什麼?
Do you want No. 1 fuckee?
你要最佳性伴嗎?
Any of you boys want No. 1 fuckee?
你們誰要最佳性伴?
I'm so horny I can't even get a piece of hand!
我慾火焚身連自慰也不夠
Me want suckee.
我要被吸老二
Suckee, fuckee, she give you everything you want.
吸老二 做愛 她為你們...
Long time.
長時間服務
Everything you want! All right!How much, chief?
我們需要的一切 多少錢?
$15 each.
每人十五美元
$15 beaucoup money.
十五元太貴了
$5 each.
每人五元
Come on, she love you good.Boom-boom long time. $10.
她愛你們 長時間 十元
$5.No, $10.
- 五元 - 不 十元
Trade you some ARVN rifles.
有南越軍步槍給你
Never been fired and only dropped once.
從未發射只墜地一次
Okay, $5. You give me.
好吧 你給我五元
Let's get mounted.
我們去尋歡作樂
Something wrong, chief?
有什麼不妥?
She says no boom-boom with you.
她說不願和你做愛
What the motherfuck?
她媽的怎麼回事?
She says soul brother too beaucoup.
她說黑人老二過大
He's saying you black boys pack too much meat!
她說你們黑人老二過大
She looks like she could suck the chrome off a trailer hitch.
她自己似乎也有大陰道
She say too beaucoup. Too beaucoup.
她過份雄偉
Excuse me, ma'am.
對不起 女士
What we have here is a magnificent...
這裏有一條優秀...
...specimen of pure Alabama blacksnake.
阿拉巴馬純種黑蛇
But it ain't too goddamn beaucoup.
牠不會過於巨大
Okay. Okay.
好吧 好吧
We need a batting order.
要安排打擊順序
I'm going first.
我是第一棒
Back off, white bread.Don't get between a dog and his meat.
別插隊 白肉仔 不要阻礙
All fucking niggers must fucking hang.
所有該死黑鬼都該處絞刑
Hey, I won't be long.I'll skip the foreplay.
我不會太久 省略愛撫前奏
I don't want it after you, man!
我不願在你後面
Intelligence passed the word down...
根據我軍情報...
...that during the night the N. V.A. pulled out of our area...
北越軍在晚上已撤離我們區域
...to positions across the Perfume River.
退往香河另一端防守
Our squad is sent on patrol to check out the report.
我們一隊前往巡邏證實情報
Face outboard and take cover! Do it!
面向前掩護自己
He ain't going to make it.
他活不了
Hotel One Actual, this is Cowboy.
一號旅館陣亡一人 這是牛仔
Murph, this is Cowboy.Crazy's hit. Booby trap.
墨菲 狂人中詭雷喪生
Wait one.
明白了 等一分鐘
You're senior NCO. Take charge and continue with the patrol.
你是高級士官 繼續負責巡邏
Call in at the next checkpoint. Over.
下一檢驗點聯絡
Roger. Understand.
瞭解
I'm squad leader.
我已升任班長
I'll follow you anywhere, scumbag.
我願跟你去任何地方
He's dead.
他死了
What's up?
什麼事?
We made a mistake at the last checkpoint.
我們上一檢驗點走錯路
See what you think.
你有何主張?
I think we're here...
我想我們在這裏
...and we should be here.
我們該在這裏
We're here?
我們在這裏嗎?
We should be here?
我們現在這裏嗎?
What do you think?
你認為怎樣?
I think we should change direction.
我們該改變方向
We'll change direction.
我們改變方向
What's up?
發生什麼?
Change in direction.
改換方向
Are we lost?
我們迷路嗎?
Joker, shut the fuck up!
小丑 閉嘴
Okay, listen up!Can you hear me?
聽著 你們能聽到我嗎?
We're changing direction.
我們改變方向前進
We're heading over that way.
我們正朝著那方向前進
Eightball's going to find a way through.
八球沒法找路通過
Got it?
你們明白嗎?
Eightball, let's dance.
八球 我們走吧
Put a nigger behind the trigger.
黑鬼總執行危險任務
Cease fire, goddamn it!
停止射擊 該死
Cool it, goddamn it!
冷靜點 他媽的
Cease fire!
停上射擊
Listen up! Did anybody see a sniper?
有人見到狙擊手嗎?
Did anybody see anything?
有敵軍嗎?
Negative!
沒有
Save your ammo!
節省彈藥
Nobody fire till I tell you!
我下令方可射擊
No! Cease fire! Cease fire!
停止射擊
Animal, cease fire!
野獸 停火
It's Sergeant Murphy.
墨菲中士來電話
Cowboy. Over.
我是牛仔 通話
Murphy. What is your present position? Over.
你們現在什麼位置?
Receiving enemy sniper fire.
受狙擊手射擊
Eightball is down.
八球中彈
We're half a klick north of checkpoint No. 4.
我們在第四檢驗點北半公里
Possible strong enemy forces in front of us.
我們前面可能有強大敵軍
Request immediate tank support. Over.
請求立刻增援坦克
Roger. Understand.
知道了
I'll see what I can do. Over.
我沒法處理
Stay close.
緊跟隨我
Listen up! I think we're being set up for an ambush.
我們被誘入陷阱中伏
There may be strong enemy forces in those buildings.
那些大樓可能藏有大量敵軍
I've requested tank support.
我已請求坦克增援
We'll sit tight...
守在此地...
...but keep our eyes open.
提高警惕
If they hit us...
如遭敵軍攻擊...
...we'll have to pull back fast.
我們將被迫撤退
Goddamn it! Cease your fire, Mother!
該死
Cease your fucking fire!
野獸 停止射擊
We can't leave him!
不能留下八球在那裏
We'll get him when the tank comes up.
坦克來後我們去救他
He's hit three times!
他中彈三次
He can't wait!
不能等
That sniper's just trying to suck us in one at a time.
那狙擊手企圖逐個射殺我們
Goddamn it!
該死
No!
停止射擊
Goddamn it
他媽的
cease fire!
停火
Fuck this shit!
管他媽的
I'm going in to bring him out!
我去救八球
Sit the fuck down
坐下
goddamn it!
該死
Okay, cease fire! He's there!
停火 他已到達
Hold your fire!
停止射擊
You can't see the sniper!
你們看不見狙擊手
Save the ammo!
節省彈藥
Nobody fire till I tell you! Nobody!
無我命令不得射擊
Hold your fire!
停止射擊
What the fuck do we do now?
我們如何分辨呢?
Give me that fucking radio.
給我無線電話
Murph? This is Cowboy. Over.
墨菲 這是牛仔
We're in deep shit. Two men down.
我們有麻煩 二人中彈
What's the story on the tank? Over.
坦克有何消息?
Sorry, Cowboy.
抱歉
No luck so far with the tank.
暫不能增援坦克
Will advise. Over.
隨時和你通訊
Numb- nut bastards.
愚蠢的雜種
Okay, listen up!
你們聽著
Can't wait for the tank.
不能再等坦克
They're going to hit us any minute.
敵軍隨時攻擊我們
When they do, we won't have time.
那時已太遲 我們現在...
We have to pull out now. Get ready.
須撤退 準備
Wait! Hold it!
等一下 且慢
Nobody's pulling out!
沒有人 撤退
There's only one fucking sniper!
只有一名狙擊手
Back off!I'm calling the plays
閉嘴 我負責指揮
and I say we pull out!
我下令後撤
What about Doc Jay and Eightball?
醫生和八球怎麼?
It's shitty, but we can't refuse
情況危急
to accept the situation.
我們必須接受現實
We're not leaving them out there!
我們不能留下他們
You know that! They're wasted!
你知道他們必死無疑
Come on, we gotta bring them back.
我們現在就去扶他們回來
Let's do it!
立刻去!
Stand down!
不准去
That's a direct order.
這是直接命令
Fuck you, Cowboy!
去你的 牛仔
Fuck all you assholes!
去你們笨蛋
Goddamn it!
該死
Fucking son of a bitch!
該死狗養的
You motherfucker!
你這渾蛋
Where's the sniper?
狙擊手在哪裏?
Doc
醫生
where's the sniper?
狙擊手在哪裏?
Shit!
該死
他媽的
Fuck!
該死
Doc Jay and Eightball are wasted!
醫生和八球都死了
There's only one sniper!
只有一名狙擊手
Move up the squad!
小隊可前進
You're clear up to here!
我這裏安全
Son of a bitch.
那個狗養的
No-Doze, Stutten, Donlon, Rock,
不准瞌睡 史 唐 岩石
come with me. We'll take a look.
跟我來 我們去偵察
You stay put and cover our ass!
其餘人掩護我們...
We may come back in a big hurry!
我們或許很快回來
I'm going with you.
我跟你去
I'm coming, too.
我也去
All set?
準備妥當嗎?
Let's move!
我們走吧
Top of the building,
他在屋頂
round the corner.
轉角那裏
Give me that radio.
給我無線電話
This is Cowboy. Over.
這是牛仔 通話
Holy shit! The sniper has a clean shot
狙擊手視線清楚
through the hole!
把他抬出去
That son of a bitch!
那個狗養的
You'll be all right.
你會沒事的
Don't shit me, Joker!
別向我說謊 小丑
I'm not. You're my favorite turd.
我不說謊 你是我好友
Hang on, man! Hang on!
撐住
I can hack it.
我能活命
我能生存
Let's go get some payback.
我們去復仇
Okay.
好吧
Watch that fucking hole.
注意那該死的洞
Give them some smoke.
放煙霧彈掩護
Ready?
準備好嗎?
Donlon, Rock, that way.
唐 岩石去那邊
You two, with me.
你們二人跟我來
Joker, in there! New Guy!
小丑 菜鳥入內
We got the sniper!
我們射中狙擊手
What's up?
發生什麼事?
We got the sniper.
我們射中狙擊手
I saved Joker's ass.
我救小丑一命
I got the sniper.
我射中狙擊手
I fucking blew her away!
我取她的命
Am I bad?
我是否了不起?
Am I a life-taker?Am I a heartbreaker?
我是否傷女人心?
What's she saying?
她在說什麼?
She's praying.
她在祈禱
No more boom-boom for this baby-san.
這女孩不能再和人做愛了
There's nothing we can do for her.
我們對她已無能為力
She's dead meat.
她必死無疑
Okay,Let's get the fuck out of here.
好吧 我們離開吧
What about her?
如何處理她?
Fuck her.
管她媽的
Let her rot.
讓她在此腐爛
We can't just leave her here.
不能丟下她
Hey, asshole...
喂 白癡...
...Cowboy's wasted.
牛仔已死
You're fresh out of friends.
你喪失好朋友
I'm running this squad now.
我現在率領這小隊
And I say we leave the gook for the mother-loving rats.
把這越共女孩喂老鼠
I'm not trying to run this squad.
我不試圖指揮這小隊
I'm just saying we can't leave her like this.
我只認為不能棄她在此
Shoot...me.
射死我
Shoot...
...me.
...我
If you want to waste her, go on...
你如果要殺她...
...waste her.
就殺她吧
Shoot.
射擊
We'll have to put you up
我們須推薦授予你
for the Congressional Medal of...Ugly!
國會最醜陋勳章
Hardcore, man.
你是冷酷無情的軍人
Fucking hardcore.
該死的冷酷無情
We have nailed our names.
我們今天足夠在歷史一頁...
in the pages of history enough for today
刻下我們姓名
We hump down to the Perfume River to set in for the night.
我們開赴香河紮營過夜
"We play fair and we work hard
我們處事公正工作勤奮
And we're in harmony
相處和諧
M-I-C-K-E-Y M-O-U-S-E
米老鼠
Forever let us hold our banner high
讓我們永遠高舉旗幟
Boys and girls from far and near
遠近各處男孩女孩
You're welcome as can be
無限歡迎你們
"M-I-C-K-E-Y M-O-U-S-E
米老鼠
"Who's the leader of the club...."
他是俱樂部領銜
My thoughts drift back to erect-nipple wet dreams...
我回憶作春夢遺精
...about Mary Jane Rottencrotch and the great homecoming fuck fantasy.
幻想和校中最美女生纏綿
I am so happy that I am alive...
我很慶幸自己仍活在世上
...in one piece, and short.
安然無恙
I'm in a world of shit, yes.
我曾出生入死險象環生
But I am alive.
但我現在仍活命
And I am not afraid.
並且我也不害怕